<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

	<title>The Spinning Arrow</title>

	<link href="http://sahil.me/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="http://sahil.me/blog"/>

	<updated>2012-12-15T16:03:57+08:00</updated>
	<id>http://sahil.me/blog</id>

	<author>
		<name>Sahil Bajaj</name>
		<email>sahil@sahil.me</email>
	</author>

	
	<entry>
		<title>On my mind</title>
		<link href="http://sahil.me//blog/posts/on-my-mind"/>
		<updated>2012-08-05T05:20:00+08:00</updated>
		<id>http://sahil.me//blog/posts/on-my-mind</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All the people I want to, no need to talk to. Some conversations are way overdue.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Red Cross AGM report.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Stupid &lt;a href='http://sce.ntu.edu.sg/CurrentStudents/Undergraduate/Pages/IndustrialAttachment.aspx'&gt;IA&lt;/a&gt; log book. (We have to write a log book?! It&amp;#8217;s like being in school, sheesh)&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;CSC301 Programming Languages past-year paper solution, which I so wisely gave my name for solving.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;All the open tabs on my browser that I want to read.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href='http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artemis_Fowl:_The_Last_Guardian'&gt;new Artemis Fowl&lt;/a&gt;! Why are books so expensive abroad?&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;New blog. Well technically, new home for this blog. And bye bye, Blogger.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Work.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Weekends are too short.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Regularity is simultaneously helpful and mundane. And tiring.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;A lot of pending blog posts.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Worrying about sleeping on time is rather depressing.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;1 is actually on my mind quite a bit, I realize.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;So is all the Red Cross related stuff.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Gah!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PS&lt;/strong&gt;. Dreary days make me want to listen to music and go off somewhere. Preferably both.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Hang on... don't I have a PSP?</title>
		<link href="http://sahil.me//blog/posts/hang-on-dont-i-have-psp"/>
		<updated>2012-06-19T04:17:00+08:00</updated>
		<id>http://sahil.me//blog/posts/hang-on-dont-i-have-psp</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#8217;m not much of a gamer (unless you count occasional bouts of Quake III, Portal or Counter Strike), but I do own one of those oldfangled handheld consoles, i.e., the &lt;a href='http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Playstation_portable#PSP-3000'&gt;PlayStation Portable&lt;/a&gt;. It was my eternal seventh-grade dream to own a &lt;a href='http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gba#Game_Boy_Advance_SP'&gt;GameBoy Advance&lt;/a&gt;; I finally realized it three years ago by buying a PSP instead and promptly spent the subsequent three years not purchasing a single game for the platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, I salvaged it from the drawer it had been kept hidden in, discovered a depressing growth of mould on the analog stick, charged it thanks to a certain someone, and finally decided to take the plunge and try to install custom firmware on it (if you have no idea what that means, I suppose it&amp;#8217;s something like jailbreaking an iPhone). In the days of yore, one had to do all kinds of complicated things involving things with names like “Pandora battery” and feverishly crossed fingers so it&amp;#8217;s not too surprising that that – combined with the fact that my cutting-edge PSP couldn&amp;#8217;t even &lt;em&gt;be&lt;/em&gt; modded in the first place – prevented me from blemishing its internal pristinity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then yesterday I decided to take a look at How Things Stood in the mire of modded PSPs and, lo and behold! it can now be accomplished in the astronomical number of three short steps which took me all of half a minute to complete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The result, you ask? Witness my &lt;em&gt;magnum opus&lt;/em&gt; (for the day, that is):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src='http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-uUwyEwBs3MM/T99L44fzfGI/AAAAAAAAAZU/YUIVBAb2DKo/s1600/psp-gba.png' /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;a href='http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kirby_(series)'&gt;Kirby&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href='http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Street_Fighter'&gt;Street Fighter&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href='http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mario'&gt;Mario&lt;/a&gt;. Of the &lt;em&gt;GameBoy Advance&lt;/em&gt; variety.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The GameBoy obsessions of my younger self are purely coincidental, but yes, I spent my day playing old Nintendo GBA games on a not-so-old Sony PSP. The mind, it &lt;em&gt;boggles&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PS&lt;/strong&gt;. Does anyone know how to incinerate mould so I may never again have to groan in irked displeasure every time I see something of mine that I haven&amp;#8217;t used in a while?&lt;/p&gt;</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Bricks in the wall</title>
		<link href="http://sahil.me//blog/posts/bricks-in-wall"/>
		<updated>2012-06-18T02:13:00+08:00</updated>
		<id>http://sahil.me//blog/posts/bricks-in-wall</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Back! I shall be! No, I &lt;em&gt;am&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
	</entry>
	

</feed>